Meron Molla

Junior Data Analyst | SQL Server

Diligent customer service and cashier boasts over five years of experience. Recently achieved an MSc in Computer Science and completed the Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate. Entrylevel data analytics professional proficient in data wrangling, modeling, visualization, and reporting using SQL, Excel, Python, and BI tools. Strong communication, organizational, and analytical skills.

meronalebachew44@gmail.com

(919)-656-2736

Georgia, United States

meronmolla.com/

linkedin.com/in/meronmolla

WORK EXPERIENCE

Data Rater TransPerfec

08/2023 - Present

Georgia, US

Tasks

- Evaluate and rate data quality according to established guidelines, ensuring work quality.
- Utilize specialized tools and software to assess and categorize various types of data.
- Contribute insights and recommendations for process improvements to optimize data rating efficiency.

Customer service DeKalb Farmers Market

02/2017 - 09/2020

Georgia, US

Tasks

- Provided excellent customer service and achieved a high rate of client satisfaction and retention.
- Monitored, directed, and prioritized store front-end activities in a fast-paced environment.
- Answering calls and worked with my supervisor to address any outstanding issues or concerns.
- Processing and generating reports.

EDUCATION

MSc, Computer Science American College of Technology

2020 - 2022

Graduate with High Honors

Study Program

American College of Technology

Courses

- Data Warehouse and Data Mining
- Software Engineering
- Computer security and privacy
- Project Management

SKILLS



Teamwork, Multitasking, Adaptability, Research.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- MS Degree In Computer Science GPA 3.8
- SQL Server Certificate
- Google Data Analytic Certificate

PORTFOLIO PROJECTS

Please click the link below

- https://meronmolla.com/
- https://github.com/MeronMolla

LANGUAGES

English
Full Professional Proficiency

Amharic

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Technology

Business

Art

Education